# Anna Aghajanyan

818.747.8865• Los Angeles, CA • anna.aghajanyan987@gmail.com • <u>www.linkedin.com/in/aghajanyan-anna/</u> • www.github.com/Anna02F • www.anna02f.github.io/My-portfolio-website

## **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Creative, motivated, and passionate junior Frontend/UI Developer with extensive experience in accounting systems. Highly effective at working and collaborating with team members to accomplish projects on time. Expertise in developing user interfaces for web applications and a responsive design using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React, and other UI technologies.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## UI Engineer, Kaput.am. Game startup, remote

01.2021 to 02.2022

Kaput.am is a fast-growing game startup that delivers online gaming experiences. Working as a side project.

- Increased user interaction by 10% using competitive analysis and research.
- Gathered user requirements, designed new UI elements, and got positive feedback from users.
- Collaborated with a team to unpack user issues and find solutions in the most effective ways.
- Involved in using GIT for project management and version control.

## **UI Engineer Intern**, **TCO LLC**, remote

06.2019 to 06.2019

TCO LLC is an Armenian-based IT Startup, where I started my training and career as a UI Engineer intern.

- Converted design mockups into functional web applications using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap.
- Provided full testing, speed optimization, and accessible and usable products.
- Designed web pages and used applications that meet business and user goals through a positive user experience.

### Accountant, ARMECONOMBANK OJSC, Yerevan, Armenia

12.2016 to 10.2018

ARMECONOMBANK is one of the largest banks in Armenia. Worked in a customer-centered environment.

- Performed all duties with high responsibility to ensure all deadlines were met on time.
- Ensured customer satisfaction with patience, open-mindedness, and a positive attitude.
- Processed 30+ customer transactions per hour with extreme attention to detail.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- HTML, CSS, SCSS, React, JavaScript, Bootstrap
- Responsive design, Browser Compatibility
- SEO best practices, Usability, Accessibility
- Basic Back-End: Node.js
- Version Control: Git

#### **EDUCATION**

**Armenian State University of Economics,** Master of Finance, Major in Securities Markets, *2014 to 2016* **Armenian State University of Economics,** Bachelor of Finance, Major in Securities Markets, *2010 to 2014*